Do you consider yourself a politician?
Well, at this point, I'm running for president.
So it would be disingenuous for me to say I'm not.
I mean, I'm running for president, so.
I'll press you on that.
And this is why.
In my opinion, I feel like what happened is we have a nation that is now run by politicians
versus public servants.
At one point, I think a lot of us felt like we were electing people that were serving
on our behalf.
And so it was clear in their job title as a public servant that they are serving on the
behalf of the public that elected them.
Somehow over time, though, this became bastardized into this title of politician, which is actually
not about serving the people, but it's actually about being political, doing a dance of verbiage,
of litigation, of lobbying, et cetera.
It's very much corporate bullshit, right?
It's just a different name for the corporate bullshit that we see in corporations, the per
my previous email behavior.